Now, we have learned precision and recall so as we've
我们已经学习了精度和召回率
医疗模型的精度是 55.7%
seen our medical model has a precision of 55.7%,
召回率是 83.3%
and a recall of 83.3%.
It's supposed to be a hierarchical model.
它应该是个层次模型
垃圾邮件检测器的精度是 76.9% 召回率是 37%
Our spam detector has the precision of 76.9% and a recall of 37%,
and it's supposed to be a high-precision model.
它应该是个高精度模型
现在的问题是 我们需要始终计算两个数字吗？
Now the question is, do we want to be carrying two numbers around all the time?
Do we want to carry precision in one pocket and recall in the other one,
我们需要在一个口袋里装着精度 另一个装着召回率
然后任何时候做出决策时
and always be looking at both,
始终查看这两个值吗？
any time we make a decision?
这样不太方便吧？
Well that's inconvenient, right?
我们只希望计算一个得分
We kind of want to only have one score.
问题是 如何将这两个得分合二为一？
So the question is, how do we combine these two scores into one?
Can we think of a way?
能找出一种方式吗？
很简单的方法是计算平均值 对吧
Well, a pretty simple way, is taking the average, right?
我们计算精度和召回率的平均值
So let's take the average of precision and recall.
左侧是 69.5%
In the left, we get 69.5%,
in the right, we get 56.95%.
右侧是 56.95%
指标还可以
And that's an okay metric,
但是我相信你可能会想到
but I'm sure you're probably thinking in your head,
与准确率没啥区别吧
that's not very different than accuracy, right?
That's not saying too much.
提供的信息并不多
判断这种平均值并不是最佳策略的方法是
And the way to see how this average is not the best idea,
is to try and in the extreme examples,
尝试一些极端示例
例如信用卡欺诈示例
so the credit card fraud example.
So again, we have a bunch of good and fraudulent credit card transactions.
我们有一堆良好的信用卡交易和欺诈性交易
我们选择一个糟糕的模型 1
And let's pick a terrible model one,
which says, all transactions are good.
该模型表示所有交易都是良好的交易
So what does the precision of this model?
这个模型的精度是多少？
Well the precision is, out of the ones we classified as bad,
精度是分类为欺诈性的交易当中
有多少是欺诈性交易
how many of them are bad?
这个数字有问题 因为我们没有将任何交易标记为欺诈性交易
That's a questionable number, because we didn't label anything as fraudulent,
就相当于 0 除以 0 这是不可取的
so it's kind of zero divided by zero which is undefined.
But it makes sense to think of it as 100%, right?
但是可以看做 100% 对吧
Since we made zero mistakes among the ones who predicted positive,
因为在预测为阳性的数据点当中 我们犯了 0 个错误
which is a precision tries to measure.
也就是我们尝试衡量的精度
So let's say this model has a 100% precision.
假设这个模型的精度是 100%
Now, as for the recall, the recall is,
召回率则是
how many of the fraudulent transactions do we catch?
我们发现了多少欺诈性交易
Well since we caught none,
因为一个也没发现
this number is zero.
所以该数字是 0
精度和召回率的平均值是 50%
So the average between precision and recall is 50%,
since it's the average of a hundred and zero.
也就是 100 和 0 的平均值
现在的问题是 这个糟糕模型的得分可以是 50% 吗？
Now the question is, do I want to give this horrendous model of 50%?
对如此糟糕的模型来说 似乎很高
It kind of seems like a really high score for such a lousy model.
我其实希望给它一个非常低的得分 甚至是 0
I kind of want to give it a much lower score, perhaps even zero.
看来平均值并不理想 我们再看看相对立的情形
For average is not that good. Now, let's try the opposite.
假设模型表示所有交易都是欺诈性交易
Let's try the model that says that all transactions are fraudulent.
该模型的精度是多少？
What is the precision of this model?
Well, out of all the transactions that are said are fraudulent,
在所有表示为欺诈性的交易当中
472 were actually fraudulent.
472 个实际上是欺诈性交易
因此精度是 472/284,807 等于 0.16%
So the precision is 472 divided by 284,807, which is 0.16%.
召回率实际上很高
And the recall is actually pretty good,
because out of the 472 fraudulent transactions, I caught all of them.
因为在 472 个欺诈性交易中 我发现了所有的交易
因此召回率是 472/472 等于 100%
So the recall is 472 divided by 472 which is 100%.
二者的平均值是 0.16 和 100 的均值 结果为 50.08
So again, the average of the two is the average of .16 on a hundred, which is 50.08.
对于这个糟糕的模型来说 得分很高了
Again, a very high score for a really lousy model.
我们希望给其一个更低的得分
So we want to give it a lower score,
或许接近 0 的值
maybe something close to zero.
So in summary, average is not the greatest thing in
总结下 如果精度或召回率非常低的话
principle if either precision or recall is very low.
那么平均值就不太合适
We want the number to be low,
我们希望得分很低
虽然另一个数字很高
even if the other one is high.
现在介绍一个解决方案
So here's a solution.
还有一种平均值 叫做调和平均数
There's another type of average called the harmonic mean,
and it works as follows.
原理如下
假设有两个数字 X 和 Y X 小于 Y
Let's say we have two numbers X and Y. X is smaller than Y,
这是算术平均数
and we have the arithmetic mean over here.
也就是 (x+y)/2
That is the average X plus Y divided by two.
然后是调和平均数
And we have something called the harmonic mean,
即 2xy/(x+y)
which is defined by two X Y divided by X plus Y.
And it's kind of an average two,
它也是一种平均值
如果两个数字相等
in the sense that if the two numbers are equal,
则得出 X 或 Y
we get X or Y,
and it always lies between X and Y.
它始终在 X 和 Y 之间
但实际上调和平均数始终
But actually, it's a mathematical fact that
the harmonic mean is always less than the arithmetic mean.
小于算术平均数 这是个数学现象
So it's kind of closer to the smaller number,
因此与更大的数字相比
than to the higher number.
它更接近于更小的数字
So it's a good example if the precision is one and the recall is zero.
如果精度是 1 召回率是 0
The average is 0.5, but the harmonic mean is,
则平均值是 0.5 但调和平均数是
代入公式的话 结果是 0
if you plug it in the formula, zero.
Another example, if the precision is 0.2 and the recall is 0.8,
再看个示例 如果精度是 0.2 召回率是 0.8
那么算术平均数是 0.5
then the arithmetic mean is 0.5,
but the harmonic mean is 0.32.
但是调和平均数是 0.32
So it closer to the lower number.
因此更接近更低的数字
从现在开始 我们不再使用平均值或算术平均数
So from now on, we will not be using the average or arithmetic mean,
but we will be using the harmonic mean.
而是使用调和平均数
它就叫做 F1 得分
And that's going to be called F1 score.
正如我们提到的 F1 得分更接近于精度和召回率中最小的值
And as we said, the F1 score is closer to the smallest between precision and recall.
因此如果其中一个值非常低
So if one of this particularly low,
那么 F1 得分就会发出提醒
the F1 score kind of raises a flag.
平均值就相当于如果一个值不错
The average kind of says, if one is good,
但另一个很糟糕 那么平均值还可以
but the other one is bad, then the average is okay.
但是对于 F1 得分来说
But the F1 score,
如果其中一个值很小 它就会发出提醒
raises the flag if one of them is small.
我们现在可以回到信用卡欺诈示例并计算 F1 得分
So we can now go back to the credit card fraud example and calculate the F1 score.
Since it's going to be the harmonic mean between the precision which is 100%,
因为它是精度（即 100%）和召回率（即 0）
and the recall which is zero.
之间的调和平均数
We can plug in the formula,
我们代入公式里
and actually get an F1 score of zero.
得出 F1 得分为 0
This is much closer to what the models should score.
这个与模型应该获得的得分接近多了
So, in the following two quizzes,
在下面的两道测验中
we'll let you calculate the F1 score of the medical model and the spam email model.
我们将请你计算医疗模型和垃圾邮件模型的 F1 得分